let questions=[
    {
        numb:1,
        question:"Javascript is an __________ language?",
        answer:"A. Object-Oriented",
        options:[
            "A. Object-Oriented",
            "B. Object-Based",
            "C. Procedural ",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question:"Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in javascript?",
        answer:"C. Both A and B",
        options:[
            "A. var",
            "B. let",
            "C. Both A and B",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question:"Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
        answer:"C. Both A and B",
        options:[
            "A. getElementbyId()",
            "B. getElementsByClassName()",
            "C. Both A and B",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question:"How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        answer:"A. const",
        options:[
            "A. const",
            "B. let",
            "C. var",
            "D. constant"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question:"What Keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
        answer:"A. in",
        options:[
            "A. in",
            "B. is in",
            "C. exists",
            "D. lies"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question:"Which CSS property allows you to set multiple list properties at once?",
        answer:"B. List-Style",
        options:[
            "A. List-Style-Type",
            "B. List-Style",
            "C. List-Style-Position",
            "D. List-Style-Image"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question:"How can you write into HTML output using Java Script?",
        answer:"C. document.write()",
        options:[
            "A. innerHTML",
            "B. console.log()",
            "C. document.write()",
            "D. window.alert()"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question:"Elements between and tags of HTML tables are _____ by default?",
        answer:"B. left aligned",
        options:[
            "A. justified",
            "B. left aligned",
            "C. right aligned",
            "D. center aligned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question:"The basic elements of a form are called:?",
        answer:"D. controls",
        options:[
            "A. objects",
            "B. table",
            "C. record",
            "D. controls"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question:"What is the latest version of CSS avaliable?",
        answer:"B. CSS3",
        options:[
            "A. CSS2",
            "B. CSS3",
            "C. CSS3.1",
            "D. CSS4"
        ]
    },
    
];